High school teachers of Reddit. What's the most
awkward position a student has ever put you
in. A ninth grade student in my world
history class came to my classroom after school
to make up a quiz? She sat down
across from my desk and when I looked
up, I noticed that her shirt was un
button almost completely down to her waist. She
had a scarf on. So at a glance
she just looked normal. But she definitely un
button or shirt almost all the way down
right before entering my classroom, alone. I honestly
thought for a second that the school may
have paid her to test how much integrity
had as a male teacher. It was uncomfortable.
Edit should have been more clear. School policy
was to keep the door open when alone
with any students regardless of gender, which it
was. It was right after school, so there
was still a lot of activity in the
hallways, her being in there with a door
open wasn't out of the ordinary at all.
The way she was sitting kept anyone in
the hallway from seeing what she had done.
Which made it even more awkward. I just
didn't look at her acted like I didn't
notice. She never did anything like that around
me for the rest of the year,