*Obligatory
throwaway
because.....
Literally no
one cares.
*I don't know
why but it's
the
I'll see myself
out
after a joke
*RIP your DMs
More a
commentary on
the average
redditor than
the one who
puts this as a
comment.
*This guy
Reddits.
*
This.
*Edit: thanks
for the
upvotes!
edit edit:
wow guys didnt
expect the
support.
thanks for the
upvotes!
edit edit edit:
this blew up
overnight!
thanks guys
*
shut up and
take my up
vote
or
take my up vote
and get out
*OK.
That's enough
Reddit for
today.
*Can't believe
I had to
scroll down so
much to find
this.
*
This is a
throwaway
because my
family uses
Reddit...
proceeds to
type out very
specific
family drama
that they'll
recognize
immediately no
matter what
account it's
posted from